

CONTACTS



Yasser.rahmeh94@gmail.com



+964 7706634056



Erbil

YASSER KHALED RAHME

Dear Sir,

I am a man with great motivation, ambition and expectations, as I believe in my experience in administration, marketing and communicating with beneficiaries and clients even from other cultures, so I have the desire to be an active member of your great company by working in this position.

I am so sure that I can handle the required responsibilities and able to achieve any assigned task, cause I am hardworking with keen eye on details.

Best regards,

Thanks in advance.

EXPERIENCE

SALES SUPERVISOR

ETC

(Educational Trust Center)

JUN 2017 - May 2021

SYRIA-HAMA-SALAMIEH

Responsibilities:

- Holding meetings with clients inside and outside the center to establish new cooperation with them.
- Introducing the courses to new students.
- Create unique marketing methods, which increase the amount of revenue and make potential clients actual ones.
- Scheduling and organizing activities to determine the priorities of work.

Employee Marketing Department

2015 - 2016

Stryker Corporation (Medical Services)

SYRIA-LATTAKIA

Responsibilities:

- Direct field marketing of the company's products and medical services in a professional manner.
- Negotiating the companies and hospitals to sign contracts and making profitable deals by conducting meetings with different people from different cultures to earn the client satisfaction.
- Coordinating dealing with hospitals and contracted companies and following up to ensure a sustain dealing.

COMPUTER SKILLS

Proficiency	Computer Skill Name
expert	Microsoft Office Programs
expert	E _Marketing- Networking

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY DEGREE

2016 - till now

Syrian Virtual University

Information Technology (Information systems and data NETWORKS).

INSTITUTE DIPLOMA

2014 - 2016

Tishreen University

Commerce & Economics (Banking & Financing)

TRAINING COURSES

Course Name	Training Center
Training of trainers	Syria Trust for Development
Project Management	Aga Khan Foundation
Office Management	Aga Khan Foundation
Bioenergy human	Quality International certification LTD.UK (British Board)
Diploma of Neuro Linguistic programming	International Center for Human Construction (American Board)
Time Management	International Center for Human Construction

REFERENCES:

Name Organization Position **Emails** yamen_daoud@outlook **ETC Training** Mr. Yamen Daoud **Branch Manager** .com Center AgaKhan Mr. Talaat Zaino Career Counselor talaat.zaino@akdn.org Foundation AgaKhan Quality Ms. Razan Adra razan.adra@akdn.org Foundation Assurance Officer

HOBBIES

(Documenting)



